# **TU LANG PHIEU**

Phone: +84.979.398.849.

Email: <u>tulangphieu@gmail.com</u>

## Personal details

Phuoc Hai commune, Ninh Phuoc District, Ninh Thuan Province. Permanent Temporary 71/26/38A Nguyen Bac, 3 Ward, Tan Binh District, Ho Chi Minh City.

Date of Brith May, 12th, 1979.

Gender Male. Nationality VietNam.

# **Career objective**

To establish a successful career, work with many challenge jobs, friendly people, pressure environment. I want to build expertise, enhances professional skills and find more experiences in hardware and software development process.

- Improve myself to be the best in specialized IT major Computer Engineering.
- Gain Success with career path, promote so far from working environment.

## **Education**

9.2007 – 8.2013	Bach Khoa University, Vietnam National University Ho Chi Minh City  Bachelor of Engineering in Computer Engineering.
5.2017 – present	Postgraduate Bach Khoa University, Vietnam National University Ho Chi Minh City.  Master in Computer Science.

## Work experience

9.2018 - present Work at Legato

Position: Software Engineer Work's achievement:

Fontend:

Framework: Bootstrap, JavaScrip, Wordpress, Codeinighter.

5.2016 - 11.2016 Work at OMC - VNPT

Position: System Engineer.

Work's achievement:

Configure equipment DSL, Switch ZTE, GPON ZTE Mini OLT ZXA10 C320, switch Alcatel Lucent OS6450, ALU OLT 7360 ISAM FX, with NET, TV include multicast and VIOD,

- Knowledge routing system cisco MAN-E through BRAS prior to that are going to ONT.
- Proper Configuration and deploying of Cisco Router Video Conferencing and Collaboration Meeting Rooms.

### 5. 2014 – 8. 2014 Work at ICDREC Vietnam National University HCMC

Project: Developer compiler chip VN8.

Position: Software Engineer.

Work's achievement: GNU binutil, building target AVR, vn8, GNU Assembler.

Tools: GNU GDB, GNU GCC. OS: Debian.

#### Thesis project at university.

Project: Building an Audio Podcast Listening Program on Altera DE2 Kit with LCD touch Module.

Subjects: thesis.

Work's achievement: Porting OS uClinux on board FPGA Altera DE2, NIOS II programming using SoPC Builder on DE2 FPGA Kit. Building application mpg123 play file mp3 in uClinux on board Altera DE2, building application graphics connect LCD display, Developer application PLAYER play file raw in uClinux on board Altera DE2, play file audio with protocol TCP/IP computer substitution server and board DE2 substitutions client - Using socket, thread, pipe.

Operating system: Ubuntu, Fedora. Tools: Quartus II, Nios IDE, C/C++.

#### Project 4

Design a program by using Verilog HDL to drive LED on Altera DE2.

Subjects: IC design

Work's achievement: Led river, seven-segment displays on the DE2 board, implement a calculator display 16x2 LCD on the DE2 board Tools: Quartus II, Verilog

## Project 3

Chat application.

Subjects: Computer Network

Work's achievement: Using Java - TCP/IP for chat application with many clients.

Tools: Eclipse - Java.

#### Project 2

Configure Router Cisco and Routing Routers

Subjects: Computer Network.

Tools: Packet tracer, Routers and switch of Cisco.

#### Project 1

Implement Tetris game on 8051-Based Board Subjects: Microcontroller programming 8051

Work's achievement: display games Tetris with Led dot matrix.

Tools: Keil C, Flash Magic.

#### Skill

• Language C/C++, Java, Verilog HDL or any other language programming

• Develop tools Visual Studio, Eclipse, Quartus II, VIM,

• Operating System Windows, Linux, Mac OS.

Foreign language English.

# **Training**

Work with many experience in company and assignments subject university.

### Soft skills

- Problem solving skill.
- Time management skill.
- Communication skill.
- Research skill.

### Other skills

- Ability work with high pressure, completed task as soon as possible
- Complete tasks sooner than deadline.
- Respect superior and always meet superior's requirements
- Can work in many different kinds of project.
- Desire to get more task if free, high studying spirits
- Team work, Sociable, friendly with colleagues, funny guy, good communication in both English and Vietnamese with other people in team.

### **Interests**

- Programming in C/C++, Java
- Technology, Science.
- Research Operation.
- Travel, Visit many places with friend, family.
- Football, Music, Game, Badminton.

## References

MSc. Tran Trung Hieu

Instructor thesis at Bach Khoa University, Ho Chi Minh City.

Tel: 0902.857.555

Email: hieutt@hcmut.edu.vn.